Zigzag!
(playful music)
♪ I am a little zigzag boy who goes this way and that ♪
♪ I never know just where to put my coat or shoes or hat ♪
(bright playful music)
♪ I am a little zigzag girl who flutters here and there ♪
♪ I never know just where to find my brush to fix my hair ♪
(brisk playful music)
(zigzag boy hums)
♪ I am a little zigzag boy who goes this way and that ♪
♪ I am a little zigzag girl who goes this way and that ♪
♪ I never know just where to put coat or shoes or hat ♪
♪ I never know just where to find my brush to fix my hair ♪
♪ So we are little zigzag people that's the way it goes ♪
♪ We never know just where to put our brushes or our clothes ♪
(zigzag girl giggles)
(playful music)